{
    "subject": "resource/The_Frank_Zappa_AAAFNRAAA_Birthday_Bundle_(2008)",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "The Frank Zappa AAAFNRAAA Birthday Bundle 2008 was released as a digital download on iTunes on December 21, 2008. It consists of five previously unreleased tracks performed by Frank Zappa, and new tracks featuring Zappa's children, producer Joe Travers and others. It is the second iTunes album by Frank Zappa, the first being The Frank Zappa AAAFNRAA Birthday Bundle (2006). (AAAFNRAA stands for \"Anything Anytime Anywhere for No Reason At All\", Zappa's motto of sorts.) The additional A in this release's title stands for \"Again\".",
    "human_readable": "The Frank Zappa AAAFNRAAA Birthday Bundle (2008) is a digital download released on iTunes on December 21, 2008.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9546414017677307,
            "question": "On which platform was The Frank Zappa AAAFNRAAA Birthday Bundle released digitally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9491020441055298,
            "question": "Is The Frank Zappa AAAFNRAAA Birthday Bundle a physical or digital release?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9483065605163574,
            "question": "When was The Frank Zappa AAAFNRAAA Birthday Bundle released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.945765495300293,
            "question": "What year was The Frank Zappa AAAFNRAAA Birthday Bundle released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9157528877258301,
            "question": "What date did The Frank Zappa AAAFNRAAA Birthday Bundle become available for download?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9026809930801392,
            "question": "Who is the artist behind The Frank Zappa AAAFNRAAA Birthday Bundle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.896307110786438,
            "question": "What format is The Frank Zappa AAAFNRAAA Birthday Bundle available in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.847446084022522,
            "question": "What is the name of the Frank Zappa release from 2008?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8277855515480042,
            "question": "What type of content is included in The Frank Zappa AAAFNRAAA Birthday Bundle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44295746088027954,
            "question": "Does the name of the release hint at any specific aspect of Frank Zappa's life or work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Frank Zappa AAAFNRAAA Birthday Bundle (2008) is a digital download released on iTunes on December 21, 2008.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1037_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of content is included in The Frank Zappa AAAFNRAAA Birthday Bundle?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1037_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the Frank Zappa release from 2008?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1037_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What format is The Frank Zappa AAAFNRAAA Birthday Bundle available in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1037_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1037_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1037_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1037_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1037_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1037_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1037_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1037_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1037_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1037_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1037_56.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided documents clearly state that \"The Frank Zappa AAAFNRAAA Birthday Bundle 2008 was released as a digital download on iTunes on December 21, 2008,\" which supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}